Guide to the Polly Shackleton papers, 1894-1997 MS2031
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- News clippings, 1935-1994; MS2031 Series 2; 4 Linear feet
  - Newspaper clippings, 1982 July 01-14 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    [from original finding aid]: "An Analyst for the Reno Road Rhubarb", Washington Post, 07/01/1982; "MEMO From Polly Shackleton", Uptown Citizen, 07/08/1982; "The Ear", Washington Post, 07/14/1982
  - Newspaper clippings, 1982 July 06 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    [from original finding aid]: "Shackleton Faces Fight", Washington Post
  - Newspaper clippings, 1982 June 23-July 01 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    [from original finding aid]: Front - "No-Fault Insurance Bill Voted", Washington Post, 06/23/1982; Back - "Ward 3 Affluence Umbrella Doesn't Cover All Residents", Washington Post, 07/01/1982
  - Newspaper clippings, 1982 June 22-24 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    [from original finding aid]: "Kane Ends Mayoral bid, Citing Money Problems; Will Seek Council Seat", Washington Post, 06/22/1982; "MEMO From Polly Shackleton", Uptown Citizen, 06/24/1982; "'Shackleton Legislation'", Uptown Citizen, 06/24/1982
  - Newspaper clippings, 1982 June 16-July 14 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    [from original finding aid]: Front - "Nurse-Midwives; Practitioners Ask Council To Approve Licensing Bill", Washington Post, 06/16/1982; Back - "Georgetown Library Friends sponsors Author's Night", The Northwest Current, 06/17/1982 --07/14/1982
  - Newspaper clippings, 1982 June 03-16 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    [from original finding aid]: "Barry Is Endorsed By 11 on Council and School Board", Washington Post, 06/15/1982; "Council Notes, Drunken-Driver Bill Toughened", Washington Post, 06/15/1982; "Polly Shackleton, Defending the budget", Northwest Current, 06/03/1982-06/16/1982
  - Newspaper clippings, 1982 June 09-10 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    [from original finding aid]: "MEMO From Polly Shackleton", Uptown Citizen, 06/10/1982; "No-Fault Bill Gets Preliminary Approval", Washington Post, 06/09/1982
  - Newspaper clippings, 1982 June 04-10 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    [from original finding aid]: "Death With Dignity Debate", Washington Post, 06/09/1982; "Group Urges Tucker to Seek At-Large Council Seat", Washington Post, 06/04/1982; "Move to Ban Drug Paraphernalia Sales Gains D.C. Council", Washington Post, 06/10/1982
  - Newspaper clippings, 1982 May-June (Box 2, Folder 10)
    [from original finding aid]: "MEMO From Polly Shackleton", Uptown Citizen, 05/27/1982; "No-Fault Bill Gets Tentative Approval in D.C.", Washington Post, 05/26/1982; "Spotlight On Aging, Nursing Home Notes", District of Columbia Office On Aging, Volume 6, No. 3, 05/1982-06/1982
  - Newspaper clippings, 1982 September 12-16 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    [from original finding aid]: Front - "City Council, Clarke Ahead in New Poll", Washington Post, 09/12/1982; Back - "MEMO From Polly Shackleton", Uptown Citizen, 09/16/1982; "Incumbents Triumph in Council Vote", Washington Post, 09/16/1982; Missing - "D.C. Citizens For Better Public Education", 09/14/1982
  - Newspaper clippings, 1982 February 15-17 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    [from original finding aid]: "Council Members Balk At Personal Check Ban", Washington Post, 02/15/1982; "First Woman Picked to Sit as Circuit Court Judge in Virginia", Washington Post, 02/17/1982
  - Newspaper clippings, 1982 February 09-10 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    [from original finding aid]: "D.C. Budget Group Asks Unspecified Arts Funds Boost", Washington Post, 02/09/1982; "Council Passes Bill to Aid Crime Victims", Washington Post, 02/10/1982
  - Newspaper clippings, 1986 November 05 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    [from original finding aid]: Front - "Clarke, Four on D.C. Council Keep Seats", Washington Post, 11/05/1986; "The District, Mayor Barry Defeats Schwartz, Wins Third Term", Washington Post, 11/05/1986; Back - "The District, Mayor Barry Defeats Schwartz, Wins Third Term", Washington Post, 11/05/1986
  - Newspaper clippings, 1986 November 06-09 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    [from original finding aid]: "Schwartz May Gain Status as D.C. Council Heads for Change", Washington Post, 11/06/1986; "D.C.'s Long-Term Mental Health Plan Criticized", Washington Post, 11/09/1986
  - Newspaper clippings, 1986 July 27-August 28 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    [from original finding aid]: Front - "D.C. Rethinks Drinking Age", Washington Post, 07/27/1986; "Barry Camp Pushing Hard For a Big Win", Washington Post, 08/10/1986; Back - "Developers Give Heavily to Ward 3 Contender", Washington Post, 08/14/1986; "3 More Hopefuls File for D.C. Mayor", Washington Post, 08/28/1986
  - Newspaper clippings, 1986 August 28-September 03 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    [from original finding aid]: Front - "Council Race In Ward 3 Hinges on Development", Washington Post, 08/28/1986; Back - "Clarke Races With the Future", Washington Post, 09/03/1986
  - Newspaper clippings, 1986 September 07-10 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    [from original finding aid]: Front - "District Campaigns' Political Paradox", Washington Post, 09/07/1986; "The D.C. Primaries", Washington Post, 09/07/1986; Back - "Barry, Clarke, Coast in D.C. Primary Races", Washington Post, 09/10/1986
  - Newspaper clippings, 1986 September 10-14 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    [from original finding aid]: Front - "Spaulding Defeated In Ward 5 Balloting", Washington Post, 09/10/1986; Back - "Fixtures in the Neighborhood", Washington Post, 09/11/1986; "Barry Concerned About Hostility in Election", Washington Post, 09/14/1986
  - Newspaper clippings, 1986 September 18-October 08 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    [from original finding aid]: Front - "MEMO From Polly Shackleton", Uptown Citizen, 09/18/1986; "Drinking Age May Rise", Washington Post, 09/23/1986; "Hill Pressure Swayed Vote on Drinking Age", Washington Post, 09/25/1986; Back - "Reeves Municipal Center Dedicated,' Washington Post, 09/28/1986; "D.C. Council Pay Raise Meets Some Opposition", Washington Post, 10/01/1986; "MEMO From Polly Shackleton", Uptown Citizen, 10/02/1986; "Some Aides Urge Barry to Wage a More Active Campaign", Washington Post, 10/08/1986
  - Newspaper clippings, 1986 October 09-20 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    [from original finding aid]: Front - "Barry Rejects 1-on-1 Debate With Schwartz", Washington Post, 10/09/1986; "MEMO From Polly Shackleton", Uptown Citizen, 10/16/1986; "For the City's Children", Washington Post, 10/16/1986; Back - "Carol Schwartz's Life: A Tale of Drive and Prejudice", Washington Post, 10/20/1986
  - Newspaper clippings, 1986 October 12-30 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    [from original finding aid]: Front - "Dialysis Practice Spurs Dispute", Washington Post, 10/12/1986; "D.C. Council Votes Itself A Pay Raise", Washington Post, 10/22/1986; "Self-Help Time at City Hall", Washington Post, 10/22/1986; Back - "D.C. Council's 'Alternative Voice,'" Washington Post, 10/27/1986; "MEMO From Polly Shackleton", Uptown Citizen, 10/30/1986; "One City, Our City", Uptown Citizen, 10/30/1986
  - Newspaper clippings, 1985 October 17-November 17 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    [from original finding aid]: Front - "Shackleton: Retirement Is Official", Washington Post, 11/17/1985; "Shackleton to retire after aiding city 30 years", Washington Times, 10/17/1985; Back - "MEMO From Polly Shackleton", Uptown Citizen, 10/17/1985; "Polly Shackleton and Her City", Washington Post, 10/19/1985; "Letters to the Editor", Washington Post, 10/21/1985
  - Newspaper clippings, 1985 October 24-November 14 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    [from original finding aid]: Front - "Think Young, Vote Young", The Current, 10/24/1985; "MEMO From Polly Shackleton", Uptown Citizen, 10/31/1985; "5 on Council Back Rent Control Referendum", Washington Post, 11/01/1985; "5 School Board Seats At Stake in D.C. Vote", Washington Post, 11/03/1986; Back - "D.C. Ends Mandatory No-Fault", Washington Post, 11/06/1985; "Rent Issue Approved Narrowly", Washington Post, 11/06/1985; "Phosphate Ban Proposed", Uptown Citizen, 11/14/1985
  - Newspaper clippings, 1985 November 14-December 12 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    [from original finding aid]: Front - "MEMO From Polly Shackleton", Uptown Citizen, 11/14/1985; "D.C. Scraps No-Fault Requirement", Washington Post, 11/20/1985; "MEMO From Polly Shackleton,' Uptown Citizen, 11/28/1985; Back - "Chessie Demands $15 Million From Park Unit for Tract",; "MEMO From Polly Shackleton", Uptown Citizen, 12/12/1985
  - Newspaper clippings, 1985 December 09-1986 January 23 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    [from original finding aid]: Front - "Nathanson Wd. 3 Candidate", Uptown Citizen, 12/12/1985; "MEMO From Polly Shackleton", Uptown Citizen, 12/09/1985; "CSX Has No Plans To Develop C&O Property for Now", Washington Post, 12/27/1985; "Welfare Pay Raises In Dispute", Washington Post, 01/09/1986; Back - "D.C. City Council Approves Entry of Big U.S. Banks", Washington Post, 01/15/1986; "Shackleton Receives COG Scull Award", Uptown Citizen, 01/23/1986
  - Newspaper clippings, 1986 January 23-07 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    [from original finding aid]: Front - "MEMO From Polly Shackleton", Uptown Citizen, 01/23/1986; "Plotkin Seeks Ward 3 Seat", Washington Post, January 29, 1986; "Lawyers and Developers Aid Nadine Winter's Campaign", Washington Post, 02/07/1986; Back - "Dixon in Council Race", Washington Post, 02/03/1986; "City Council Salutes Consumer Advocate Ralph Nader and Buyers Up", Uptown Citizen, 02/06/1986; "Dixon Seeks Council Seat", Uptown Citizen, 02/06/1986; "MEMO From Polly Shackleton", Uptown Citizen, 02/06/1986
  - Newspaper clippings, 1986 February 06-March 01 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    [from original finding aid]: Front - "Residents Protest NW Road Proposal", Washington Post, 02/06/1986; "Charity Makes Canny Move, But Canned Mall Retaliates", Washingtonian, 02/1986; "Ellington Teacher Seeking Ward 3 Seat on D.C. Council", Washington Post, 02/17/1986; Back - "MEMO From Polly Shackleton", Uptown Citizen, 02/20/1986; "Council Majority Opposes Building Prison in D.C.", Washington Post, 02/25/1986; Obituary - "Robert W. Shackleton", Washington Post, 03/01/1986
  - Newspaper clippings, 1986 March 06-26 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    [from original finding aid]: Front - "Special Anniversary Issue, Interview with Councilmember Polly Shackleton", Consumer Utility News, 03/1986; "MEMO From Polly Shackleton", Uptown Citizen, 03/06/1986; "D.C. Council Panel tones Down Critical Report", Washington Post, 03/07/1986; "4th Democrat enters Ward 3 Race", Washington Post, 03/10/1986; Back - "Contributions Pour In for Barry", Washington Post, 03/11/1986; "Group-Home Bill Emotionally Debated", Washington Post, 03/21/1986; "D.C. Council Votes Inflation Increases In Welfare Benefits", Washington Post, 03/26/1986
  - Newspaper clippings, 1986 April 03-23 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    [from original finding aid]: Front - "MEMO From Polly Shackleton", Uptown Citizen, 04/03/1986; "D.C. Home Sellers Face Delays on Settlement Checks", Washington Post, 04/05/1986; Back - "The Council's New Muscle Shows D.C. Is Growing Up", Washington Post "Outlook", April 6, 1986; "Ward 3 Hopeful Denies Being Developers' Candidate", Washington Post, 04/23/1986
  - Newspaper clippings, 1986 April 26-May 16 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    [from original finding aid]: Front - "Barry Administration Opposes Workfare Plan", Washington Post, 04/26/1986; "MEMO From Polly Shackleton", Uptown Citizen, 05/15/1986; "Volunteer Work Repaid in Kind Under D.C. Bill", Washington Post, 05/16/1986; Back - "D.C. AIDS Bill unfair to the majority of District residents", Washington Post, 05/08/1986
  - Newspaper clippings, 1986 May 18-22 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    [from original finding aid]: Front - "Barry Opens Reelection Bid With Claims of City Progress", Washington Post, 05/18/1986; Back - "Area Officials to Campaign for Metro Funding", Washington Post, 05/19/1986; "Tenant Activists Building Coalition for Council Race", Washington Post, 05/22/1986; "Nathanson Calls For New Construction Moratorium", Northwest Current, 05/22/1986
  - Newspaper clippings, 1986 May 22-June 08 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    [from original finding aid]: Front - "Tax Reform Carol Schwartz Reports", Northwest Current, 05/22/1986; "MEMO From Polly Shackleton", Uptown Citizen, 05/29/1986; "Chevy Chase Citizens Association Joint Meeting with ANC-3G"; Back - "D.C. Council Panel Puts Off Workplace Bill", Washington Post, 06/06/1986; "For Charlene Jarvis, a Crisis Filled With Political Irony", Washington Post, 06/08/1986
  - Newspaper clippings, 1986 June 10-30 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    [from original finding aid]: Front - "Stein Club Endorses Dixon", Washington Post, 06/10/1986; "Barry Campaign Raised $359,430 in 3 Months", Washington Post, 06/11/1986; "Candidates Questions on Tenant Issues", Uptown Citizens, 06/13/1986; "MEMO From Polly Shackleton", Uptown Citizen, 06/13/1986; "Welfare Bill Falters Without Key Supporters", Washington Post, 06/19/1986; Back - "Schwartz To Run for D.C. Mayor", Washington Post, 06/25/1986; "Schwartz a Loner On D.C. Council", Washington Post, 06/30/1986; "From Welfare to Work", Washington Post, 06/30/1986
  - Newspaper clippings, 1986 July 03-10 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    [from original finding aid]: Front - "Candidates Rush to File by Deadline", Washington Post, 07/03/1986; "D.C. Council Panel Approves Sharp Drop in Estate Taxes", Washington Post, 07/04/1986; Back - "Ailing Firm Given D.C. Job Grant", Washington Post, 07/10/1986
  - Newspaper clippings, 1986 July 14-16 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    [from original finding aid]: Front - "2 Lead Challenge to Spaulding in Ward 5", Washington Post, 07/14/1986; Back - "Barry Claims Authority to Build Prison", Washington Post, 07/16/1986
  - Newspaper clippings, 1986 July 17-24 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    [from original finding aid]: Front - "Heuer Praises Inheritance Tax Revisions; Shackleton Supports Strongly; Carol Schwartz Reports", Northwest Current, 07/17/1986; Back - "Schwartz: No Laughing Matter", Washington Post, 07/21/1986; "D.C. Council Backs Funds to Save Antioch", Washington Post, 07/24/1986
  - Newspaper Clippings, undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Newspaper Clippings - Stevenson Campaign, 1955-1956 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Newspaper Clipping, "Jackson Slate Swamps Rival", Circa 1964 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Washington Star
  - Newspaper Clipping, "D.C. Democrats - Two Goliaths and a David", 1964 May 01 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Washington Daily News
  - Newspaper Clipping, "The War of the D.C. Democrats", 1964 May 03 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper Clipping, "100,000 Votes Expected in D.C. Primaries Tuesday", 1964 May 03 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Sunday Star
  - Newspaper Clipping, "Vote Tally Drags, Stirs Complaints", 1964 May 06 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Newspaper Clipping, "Jackson Slate Has 2 to 1 Lead", 1964 May 06 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    The Washington Daily News
  - Newspaper Clipping, "Council Pushes 'Power' to Legal Brink", 1970 November 08 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    Washington Post
  - Newspaper Clipping, "Hopefuls Hit Party Circuit", 1971 January 08 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Newspaper Clipping, "Fauntroy Clinches Nomination", 1971 January 13 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    Evening Star
  - Newspaper Clipping, "Citizens Attack Compromise on Home Rule", 1972 August 02 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Newspaper Clipping, "Eye", 1973 June 11 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    Women's Wear Daily
  - Newspaper Clipping, "Charisma a Factor in Ward 3 Fight", 1974 September 06 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Newspaper Clipping, "Parking Lots Are Favorite Hangouts for Teen-Age Drinkers", 1975 April 01 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Newspaper Clipping, "Tax Plans Irk D.C. Business", 1975 April 13 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Newspaper Clipping, "St. Elizabeths Head Quits as Panel Studies Shift", 1975 April 29 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Newspaper Clipping, "Council Ousts Witness Yeldell", 1975 June 14 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Newspaper Clipping, "Construction Of Housing Rises Sharply", 1975 June 18 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Newspaper Clipping, "Under Home Rule, You Can Find Someone to Listen to a Complaint", 1975 July 15 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Newspaper Clipping, "What's Happening", undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
    d.c. gazette
  - Newspaper Clipping, undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper Clipping, undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
    Sentry Post
  - Newspaper Clipping, undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Boston Evening Transcript, 1935 May 15 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Boston Evening Transcript, 1935 June 15 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - The Trade Unionist, 1964 March 14 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - The Washington City Tribune, 1964 April 23 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - The Trade Unionist, 1964 April 25 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - The Observer, 1964 April 30 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - The Trade Unionist, 1964 May 02 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Washington Post; Sunday Section, 1966 March 27 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Newspaper Clipping, "World of Women", 1970 February 02 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Newspaper Clipping, "Lead Poisoning Revisited", 1970 August 23 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Newspaper Clipping, 1970 September 01 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    Washington Daily News, pgs. 5 - 8
  - Newspaper Clipping, "Potomac voyagers home at last", 1970 September 03 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - d.c. gazette, 1970 December 21-1971 January 05 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Newspaper Clipping, "We are the people (some of them) who support Joe Yeldell for Congress", 1971 January 11 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Newspaper Clipping, 1971 January 25 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    Washington Daily News, page 15
  - Newspaper Clipping, "Hyde and Chic", 1971 May 05 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Newspaper Clipping, "Letters", 1971 June 20 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    Washington Sunday Star
  - Newspaper Clipping, 1971 November 03 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    Evening Star, front page
  - Newspaper Clipping, "Bikes, Bikes Everywhere", 1971 November 28 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Potomac Current, 1972 July (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Sentry Post, 1972 October (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Sentry Post, 1973 April (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Sentry Post, 1973 September (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Sentry Post, 1973 December (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - d.c. gazette, 1974 February (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Potomac Current, 1974 March 14 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - d.c. gazette, 1974 May (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Potomac Current, 1974 May 09 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - The Georgetowner, 1974 May 15-May 19 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Washington Star-News, 1974 September 05 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - The Washington Conservationist, 1974 October (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Washington Star-News, 1974 October 24 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Uptown Citizen, 1975 January 09 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Potomac Current, 1975 January 16 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - The Georgetowner, 1975 January 22-February 04 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Potomac Current, 1975 January 30 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Newspaper Clipping, "The District's Three Dynamic Councilwomen", 1975 February 02 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    Washington Star-News
  - Potomac Current, 1975 February 13 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Uptown Citizen, 1975 February 20 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Potomac Current, 1975 April 10 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Voter's Guide, 1978 September 12 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - The Ward III Democrat, Vol. 1, No. 3, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - The Washington Times, 1985 January 28 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - New Times, 1985 January 02 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Boston Evening Transcript, 1935 July 20 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Magazine and Book Sections, pgs. 1 - 8
  - Boston Evening Transcript, 1939 February 18 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Book Reviews, pgs. 1 - 2
  - Boston Evening Transcript, 1939 May 27 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Boston Evening Transcript, 1939 August 19 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Boston Evening Transcript, 1939 September 23 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - The Sunday Star, 1956 April 29 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    pg. A6
  - The Washington Post, 1956 April 29 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    Voter's Guide, pgs. B12 - B13
  - The Washington Post, 1956 April 30 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    City Life, pgs. 21 - 22
  - The Evening Star, 1956 May 02 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    pg. A11
  - The Washington Post, 1964 May 03 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    pg. A18
  - The Washington Post, 1965 September 12 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    pg. E2
  - The Washington Post, 1971 January 11 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    pg. A10
  - The Washington Afro-American, 1971 March 27 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    pgs. 7 - 8
  - The Washington Post, 1971 May 17 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    pg. B12
  - The Washington Post, 1972 September 03 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    Living in Style, pgs. M1 - M4
  - Newspaper Clipping, 1973 December 30 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    Washington Star News, pg. C3
  - The Washington, 1974 March 07 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    [Post? Newspaper name not in original finding aid] Panorama, pgs. F1 - F4
  - The Washington Post, 1974 August 04 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    Campaign '74, pgs. E1 - E8
  - The Washington Post, 1974 September 23 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    pg. A22
  - The Washington Post, 1974 October 30 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    Metro, pgs. B1 - B12
  - The Washington Post, 1975 April 04 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    Business and Finance, pgs. D9 - D10
  - The Washington Afro-American, 1975 April 26 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    pgs. 13 - 14
  - The Washington Post, 1975 July 08 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    Metro, pgs. C1 - C2
  - The Washington Post, 1978 August 03 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    District Weekly, pgs. DC1 - DC10
  - The Washington Post, 1978 August 10 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - The Washington Post, 1978 August 17 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - The District Star, 1980 September 10 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    Section B, pgs. B1 - B2
  - The District Star, 1980 December 10 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - The District Star, 1981 May 29 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Newspaper clippiongs, The Washington Afro-American, 1986 December 13 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    pgs. 5 - 8
- Photographs, 1900-1995; MS2031 Series 3; 2 Linear feet
  This series contains photographs, contact sheets, and negatives that document the life and public works of Polly Shackleton. There are both black and white and color photographs, as well as some corresponding negatives. The images date from 1900-95.
  - Negatives and Contact Prints, Miscellaneous, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Negatives, Miscellaneous, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Photograph, "Ceremonial Award by D.C. Council", undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Photograph, "D.C. Council", undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Photograph, "Father Hines", undated (Box 1, Folder 5)